(Leonard:)No.
(Page:)Then I'm afraid
you can't withdraw it.
(Sheldon:)I'm sorry. I don't recall
you saying "no backsies."
(Page:)Is there anything else?
(Sheldon:)Yes. I'd like to offer
a laudatory statement
(Sheldon:)about Howard's many excellent
qualities that I believe
(Sheldon:)will tip the scales
back in his favor.
"Howard Joel Wolowitz.
"H is for honesty,
of which he has much.
"O's for outstanding,
"which he is such.
"W's for witty,
he's quick with a joke.
(Sheldon:)A's for artistic, his ability...
" I'm sorry.
(Page:)Dr. Cooper, this matter
is already closed.
(Sheldon:)But I still have
"rd Joel Wolowitz" left to go.
(Page:)It's closed.
(Sheldon:)I don't understand
why you people
(Sheldon:)are picking on my
friend, Howard,
(Sheldon:)when there are much more serious
security threats to pursue.
(Sheldon:)For instance,
when I first met Leonard,
(Sheldon:)he was on the verge
of giving away
(Sheldon:)rocket secrets
to a North Korean spy,
(Sheldon:)and not one agent
ever investigated that.
(Page:)This is Leonard Hofstadter?